Artem Zelenskyy

armarcjob@gmail.com

in Artiom Zelenskiy

Barcelona, ESP

+34 652 454 282

Moscow, RUS

+7 901 757 32 68



Summary

All my experience I got by working in Exchange Currency Company. As soon i was graduated in Ukraine i moved to Spain where Im living 12 years. I never stopping and had a pleasure to work in many regions of Spain. Having an International work experience in Latin America, Russia and Turkey as Project Manager I got some new knowledges, through communication doing business and treating closely with new cultures all that and more gave me greater understanding working environment.

I believe that the skills and my actual experiences will helps me in new position, making me an ideal candidate for this job. I'm very interested in working for you and I'm willing to contribute all my efforts and desire to learn for becoming a part of your team. I'm a strong, perspective and dynamic person.

I'm watching forward and always dispose to hear and learn in obtaining new knowledges. If you would like to invite me for a personal interview I'll be glad to participate in

Core competencies

<u>Languages:</u> Spanish, English, Russian, Ukrainian

Planning, Organising, Communication, Initiative TeamWork, Communication, Adaptability, Motivation

Stress Tolerance, Integrity, Reliability Integrity, Decision Making, Working Standards,

Analytical Thinking, Client Service, Conflict Resolution

Professional experience —

02/2020 - present

Best And Fast Change Spain Assistant

06/2018 - 01/2020

Eurodivisas S.A Junior Operation Controller -Russia

11/2016 - 12/2017

New Experience)

- Manager of Menorca Airport Office
- Treasurer of Mallorca chain Offices
- Sale Manager in Madrid Offices
- Daily Reports
- Operation Activity Control
- Profit & Loss Reports
- Performance Control
- Daily Reports

Professional experience -

Eurodivisas S.A

Project Manager - Russia/ Turkey

05/2016 - 12/2017

- Budget Control
- Business Trips
- Work with projects according to company's unified design
- Regular Reports
- Achievement of building approvals
- Branch Layout
- Airports authorities & HQ communications

Eurodivisas S.A

Project Manager Assistant -Brazil

01/2016 - 05/2016

- Branches construction in Rio de Janeiro-Galeão
- Branch Layout
- Architectural Plans Review

Eurodivisas S.A Training

09/2015 - 12/2015

 Specialized training and qualified work in each of the next positions aimed on obtaining skills in Supervisor's, Treasurer's and On-site Manager's duties, in order to share that experience by transferring our strategies, principles, ethics and corporate rules for successful following and implementation in foreign country.

Eurodivisas S.A Process & Efficiency Department

01/2015 - 09/2015

- Working as translator that was consisted in organizing all corporate material (operational, financial, juridical etc.) which implied to learn and have well knowing how are departments of the Group working
- Preparing working standards

Eurodivisas S.A

Field Support Manager Russia - Expansion Department

08/2014 - 12/2014

- Business Trips
- · Calls & mailing
- The work aimed to maintaining existing contacts and business dialogue that was closely associated with international accompaniment for a future openings

Eurodivisas S.A Supervisor

02/2014 - 08/2014

- Commercialization of new products
- sales techniques
- communication skills
- sellings by applying marketing tools

Flippers International Removals

Operation & Removals

11/2013 - 02/2014

- Communication
- Logistics
- Monitoring

II Capriccion di Trinacria, L 'Escala

Manager of Restaurants Cain

03/2009 - 09/2013

- Make sure of profitability by balancing service with costs
- Encourages of quests satisfaction
- Checked BOH for food quality
- Hiring and training new employees
- Administration

Professional experience —

Fincas Can Rull International Sales Manager

09/2007 - 09/2008

- Calls, mailing
- Communication with Clients
- Researching
- Administration guideline and translation support
- www.comprarcasarcfinquies.com

Education -

Udemy 2020 - present	Full Stack Development -123/h (HTML, CSS3 Js, jQ, Bootstrap, PHP MySQL, Python, Git, GitHub, GitKraken, Wordpress Avocode)
2018 - 2018	"Futur" Study Center & Labour Orientation Of Madrid Certi ied in: "Airport Operations Technician" Flight Coordinator * Aeronautic Legislation* Meteorology* Flight Plans* Loading & Centering Sheets
2004 - 2009	Donetsk National University Master thesis: "International Relationships & Foreign Policy" Activity: Local University Ements & Political Researches of European Integration Process, Diplomatic mission & Service
2000 - 2004	Lisychansk Multidisciplinary Lyceum Master thesis: "History & Low"
1994 - 2000	School

Personal information

Technology skills MS Office-2010, Adobe illustrator

Interests Politic, stock market investment

Hobbies: Fitness, Snowboard, Judo

Driver Licence B